Guide to the Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
5956
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives
48 linear ft.
Records (documents), publications (documents).
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Due to the volume of material in this collection the finding aid has been divided into three sections.
Section 1: Boxes 1-22 (box 21 has not been inventoried at this time)
Section 2: Boxes 23-44
Section 3: Boxes 45-48
Subjects:
Automation.; Automobile industry and trade.; Boycotts.; Casual labor.; Child labor.; Coal trade.; Collective bargaining.; Labor disputes.; Economic history.; Vocational education.; Electronic data processing.; Employees--Attitudes.; Discrimination in employment.; Agricultural laborers.; Public contracts.; Collective bargaining -- Government employees.; Hours of labor.; Industrial relations; Job analysis; Job descriptions; Labor laws and legislation; Labor mobility; Labor unions; Labor unions and international relations; Labor unions--Political activity; Free enterprise; Profit-sharing; Railroads; Social security--Law and legislation; Textile industry; Clothing trade; Employees--Training of; Wages; Incentives in industry; Job satisfaction
Form and Genre Terms:
Records (documents); Publications (documents)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Related Collections:
5880: Archives Organization File V, Additional Company Documents
5583/1: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1
5583/2: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
5583/3: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3
5583/4: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 4. Corporate and Organizational Publications
5583/5: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5
5583/6: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 6
CONTAINER LIST
- Box 23, Folder (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Shall Strikes be Outlawed?, Publication (Box 23, Folder 1)
    By Joel Seidman. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: What Will Stop Strikes?, Publication (Box 23, Folder 1)
    By Joseph Ball; Emil Mazey; Thomas reid. Bulletin of the Town's Meeting. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Strikes and Democratic Government, Publication (Box 23, Folder 1)
    By Labor Committee of the Twentieth Century Fund. Report. Item is in English.
- Box 23, Folder (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Review of Labor-Management Disputes in 1949, Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    By Bureau of Labor Statistics. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Review of Labor-Management Disputes in 1948, Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Review of Labor-Management Disputes, 1947, Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Memorandum on Strikes in the Defense Period, Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: The Position of Labor During the War, Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    By Bureau of Nattional Affairs. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Strikes and Lockouts United States, 1941-1945, Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    By National Industrial Conference Board. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Strikes and Lockouts United States, 1916-1945, Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Wartime Strikes in American Industry, Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Strike Statistics, Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    By National Labor Relations Board. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Strikes in Jun, 1939, Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    By Fflorence Peterson. Wih rend for 1933 to August 1939. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Strikes in Defense Industries During 1940, Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    By Florence Peterson. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Strikes in Defense Industries, Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    By Legislative Reference Service. Saement Showing Basic Data for the Formulation of a Policy Toward Strikes in Defense Industries. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Strikes in Defense Industries, Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    By Legislative Reference Service. Supplementary Information to Accompany Senate Document no 52. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Strikes in Defense indstries, Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Strikes in July 1940, Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    By Florence Peterson. With Trend for 1933 to September 1940. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Strikes in 1939, Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    By From the Monthly Labor Review. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Strikes in September 1940, Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    By Florence Peterson. With Trend for 1933 to November 1940. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Strikes in December 1939, Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    By Florence Peterson. Wih Trend for 1933 to Februaty 1940. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Strikes in April 1941, Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Item 20: Strikes in 1940, Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Item 21: Strikes in June 1941, Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Item 22: Strikes in June 1940, Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    By Florence Peterson. With Trend for 1933 to August 1940. Item is in English.
- Box 23, Folder (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: On Strike at G. E., Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    By James Carey; Al Hartnett. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The 1959 Steel Strike, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    By International Affairs Department. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Wilson Story, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    By United Packinghouse Workers of America, AFL-CIO. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Minutes of Evidence, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    By Allan Flanders. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Strike Control Proposals in the Light of Railroad Industry Experience, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    By Michael Marsh. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Why there is a Strike at General Electric, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    By Al Hartnett; James Carey. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Right to Strike and the General Welfare, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    By Committee on the Church and Economic Life. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Statement to Governor Romney, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    By Detroit Newspaper Strike Commission. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: AFL-CIO Takes Action on the Kingsport Press Strike, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    By AFL-CIO. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Prospect for Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    By Frederick Zeller; Eugene Hagburg. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Strike at Carrier, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    By A Documentary. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: A Falling Strike and Some Shopworn Diversions, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    By Relations Service. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: what the Public Think about Care's Strike, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    By Relations Services. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Union Strike Votes, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Item is in English.
  - Item 15: An Unwarranted Strike Action which Youw Managemen Must Resist, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Item 16: management of Personnel Quaterly, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    By John Hutchinson; Orlando Behling; Bradford Boyd; Eric Vetter; Thomas O' Donovan. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Picketing in Labor Disputes, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    By Estelle Muraken; Rosa Deutsch; Alexander Kramer. Item is in English.
- Box 23, Folder (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Sympathetic Strikes, Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    By Estelle Murasken; Rosa Deutch. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Sit-Down Strike, Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Control of the Sit-Down Strike, Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    By Buel Patch. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Expressing the Sense of Congress on so-called Sit-Down Strikes and the Industrial Spy System, Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    By Mr. Connery. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Public and Strikes, Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    By Council for Democracy. Democracy in Action. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Sit-Down, Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Strikes, Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    By Joseph Senturia. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: What is the Solution to the Labor Crisis, Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    By Neil Jacoby; Clarence Randall; Harold Ruttenberg. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Sit-Down, Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    By William Cronin. What Happened to the Automobile Industry Since enactment of the National Labor relations Act. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Publications Concerning the Telephone Strike, Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    By National Federation of Telephone Workers. Item is in English.
- Box 23, Folder (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Labor Relations Review, Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    By Eugene Adams Keeney. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Strikes, Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    By William Goldner. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Can a Free Economy Tolerate Union Violence?, Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    By Herbert Kihler. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Kohler Worker's Story, Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    By The UAW-CIO International Union. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Nobody Wins a Strike, Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    By Benjamin Fairless. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Federal Fact-Finding Boards and Boards of Inquiry, Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    By maurice Tobin; Ewan Clague. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Work Stoppages in 1950 - Final Data, Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: What is Happenig at Kohler, Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    By Kohler of Kohler News. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Bloomfield Strike, Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Facts About the Strike at Chrysler, Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    By Chrysler Corporation. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Strikes and the Public, Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    By Carl Madden; Richard Landry; Henry Moore; James Morri; George Shultz; Arthur Sloan; Jack Stieber. Decisions for the Seventies. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: When Strike Threatens, Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    By research Institute of America. A Management Action Guide. Item is in English.
- Box 23, Folder (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Bulletin, Publication (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Box 23, Folder (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: ESOPs An Explanation for Employees, Publication (Box 23, Folder 7)
    By Committee on Finance, US Senate. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: ESOPs and TRASOPs, Publication (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Employee Stock Ownership Plans, Publication (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: The Stock Option Scandal, Publication (Box 23, Folder 7)
    By Industrial Union Department, AFL-CIO. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: An Analysis of 262 Restricted Stock Option Plans, Publication (Box 23, Folder 7)
    By Richard Smyth. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Story of Creative Capital, Publication (Box 23, Folder 7)
    By E. I. Du Pont De Nemours & Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Stock Ownership Plans for Employees, Publication (Box 23, Folder 7)
    By New York Stock Exchange. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Report of Employee Stock-Ownership Plans, Publication (Box 23, Folder 7)
    By Policyholders' Service Bureau. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Stock Option Scandal, Publication (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Box 23, Folder (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Steelmill Blues, Publication (Box 23, Folder 8)
    By Steve Packart. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Charting Steel's Progress During 1970, Publication (Box 23, Folder 8)
    By American Iron and Steel Institute. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Joint Advisory Committee on Productivity, Publication (Box 23, Folder 8)
    By United Steelworkers of America. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Basic Steel Industry, Publication (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Report of the Interagency Working Group on the Steel Industry, Publication (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Summary of Presidential Task Force Recommendations on the Steel industry and Union Policy Statement on Jobs and Steel Imports, Publication (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Collective Bargaining in the Steel Industry, Publication (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: Experimental Negotiating Agreement Development and Impact, Publication (Box 23, Folder 8)
    By Wiliam Maloney. Item is in English.
- Box 23, Folder (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Steel's Competitive Challenge, Publication (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Government and the Steel Industry, Publication (Box 23, Folder 9)
    By Joseph Block. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: An Audit of the Steel Industry, Publication (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Comparative Wage Structures in the Steel Industry of the Soviet Union and Western Countries, Publication (Box 23, Folder 9)
    By Gardner Clark. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Steel: The Near-sighted Bellwether, Publication (Box 23, Folder 9)
    By David Cushman Coyle. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Agreement Between United States Steel Corporation and the United Steelworkers of Ametica, Publication (Box 23, Folder 9)
    By Bureau of National Affairs Report. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Economics and Technology: The Case of Soviet Steel, Publication (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: A Strong Steel Industry for a Strong America, Publication (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: Economic Trends in the Steel Industry, Publication (Box 23, Folder 9)
    Facts for Management. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: A Management View of Employment Problems in the Steel Industryy for the Next Decade, Publication (Box 23, Folder 9)
    By William Caples. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Steel's Competitive Challenge, Publication (Box 23, Folder 9)
    By American iron and Steel Institute. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Statement Before the Senate Committee on Finance, Publication (Box 23, Folder 9)
    By John Roche. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Safety First in Steel, Publication (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Item 14: The Steel Import Problem, Publication (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Item 15: Stelmen of the Free World, Publication (Box 23, Folder 9)
    By Reprinted From Inland News. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The 1959 Steel Negotiations - and the Results, Publication (Box 23, Folder 9)
    By Leo Teplow. Item is in English.
- Box 23, Folder (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Business Big and Small Build America, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
    By Statement by Officials. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Why Steel?, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
    By American Iron and Steel Insitute. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Summary of Statement before the Presidential Steel Board, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
    By Enders Voorhees. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Full Facts, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
    By The Steel Companies in the Wage Case. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Facts Behind the Steel Strike, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Statement Before the Steel industry Board, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
    By Clarence Randall. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Some Anomalies in the Steel Board's Report, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
    By Theodore Iserman. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Truth about Contributory and Non-Contributory Pensions and Social Insurance, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
    By Phillip Murray. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Facts about the Steel Strike, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
    By Edward Ryerson. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Labor Dipute in the Basic Steel Industry, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
    By Report to the President. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Statement on Behalf of Bethlehem Steel Company and Bethlehem Pacific Coast Steel Corporation, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
    By Carroll Daugherty; David Cole; Samuel Rosenman. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Steelworkers' Case for Wages, Pensions and Social Insurance, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
    By Philip Murray. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Should the Steel Wage Recommendation be Accepted?, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
    By Robert Nathan; Jules Backman; Henry Hazlitt; Stanley Ruttenberg; Malcom Sharp. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Steel Wage Issue, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
    By American Metal Market. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Statement before the Presidential Board in the Matter of United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Item 16: Statement of A. B. Homer, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
    By carroll Daugherty; David Cole. In the Matter of the Issues Under te Reopening Provisions of Agreements Berween United Steelworkers of America and Bethlehem Steel Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Industry's Review, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
    By richars Bennett. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Statement for New Determination Under the Walsh-Healey Act of the Prevailing Minimm Wages, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Item 19: The Recent Steel Price Increases, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
    By Otis Brubaker. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Wages--Prices--Profits, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Item 21: Post-War Wage Determination in the Basic Steel Industry, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
    By Albert rees. Item is in English.
- Box 24, Folder (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Minutes of the 1944 Fall Conference, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    By Minutes. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Minutes of the 1944 Spring Conference, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Suggestion Systems - A Selected List of References, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    By National Society of Suggestion Systems. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: An Employee Suggestion System for the Small Plant or Store, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    By Donald Wilhelm Jr. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Suggestion Plans for Employees, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    By Metropolitan Life Insurance Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: A Simple Way to have a Successful Employee Suggestion System, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    By Personnel Materials Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Statistical Report for the Year 1954, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    By National Asociation of Suggestion Systems. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Cashing in on Ideas, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    By Merchants and Manudacturers Association. A tool for increasing job interes. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: What Employees Think of Suggestions Plans, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    By robert Gray. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Evaluating Intangible Suggestions, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Suggestion Sustems. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Statistical report for the Year 1955, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Suggestion Systems. Item is in English.
- Box 24, Folder (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Minites of the Spring 1943 Conference, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
    By National Association of Suggestion Systems. May 19, 20 1943. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Minutes of the Fall 1943 Conference, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
    By National Association of Suggestion Systems. November 3,4, 1943. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Story of United's Employees Suggestion Conference, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: War Production Drive, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
    By War Oroduction Board. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Employee Suggestion Program, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
    By US War Department. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Production Drive, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
    By US War Production Board. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Plans for Stimulating Suggestions from Employees, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
    By Beatrice Brower. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Suggestions from Employees, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
    By Clark Dickinson. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Suggestion Sustems Adoptd in Force by Industrial and Other Business Organizations, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Industrial Suggestion Systems, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
    By Industrial relations Counselors. Item is in English.
- Box 24, Folder (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Successful Suggestion Systems, Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
    By Industrial Welfare Society. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Annual Statistical Report for the Year 1957, Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: National Association of Duggestion Systems Presented at the Chicago Convention, October 29-30, 1956, Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
    By American Cyanamid Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Objectives of a Suggestion System, Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Eligibility of Suggesters, Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Administration of a Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Annual Statistical report for the Year 1959, Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Annual Statistical report for the Year 1958, Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Report on the Study of Adoption and Non Adoption Letters, Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Suggestion Boxes, Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Annual Satistical report for the Year 1956, Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: The Syndical Corporative System in Italy, Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: A Guide to Promotion and Publicity for an Effective incentive Awards Program, Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
    By United States Civil Service Commission. Item is in English.
- Box 24, Folder (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Anonymous, Partially and Fully Identified Suggestion plans, Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Annual Statistical report for the Year 1963, Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Annual Statistical report for the Year 1960, Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Annual Statistical Report for the Year 1961, Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Annual Statistical report for the Year 1962, Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Starting a Suggestion System in your Organization, Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Annual Statistical report for the Year 1965, Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Proceedings of the 24th Annual Conference, Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)
    By National Association of Suggestion Systems. October 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Suggestion Scheme: a Contribution to Morale or an Economic Transction?, Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)
    By C. C. Gorfin. Item is in English.
- Box 24, Folder (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Teaching Salaries then and Now, Publication (Box 24, Folder 5)
    By Beardsley Ruml; Sidney Tickton. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Occasional Papers from the Aft Program for Quality Educational Standards in Teaching, Publication (Box 24, Folder 5)
    By Department of Research. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Quest report on Differentiated Staffing, Publication (Box 24, Folder 5)
    By Department of research. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Occasional Papers from Quest, Publication (Box 24, Folder 5)
    By Department of Research. No. 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Occasional Papers from Quest, Publication (Box 24, Folder 5)
    By Department of Research. No. 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Occasional Papers from Quest, Publication (Box 24, Folder 5)
    By Department of Research. No. 7. Item is in English.